www.trangerthings.com www.behance.net/trangtt42714e5 trangtt427@gmail.com (925) 352-3373

Profile

I'm a creative who has had over seven years of designing responsive graphic interfaces and all other accompanying assets. I specialize in building products that are useful, intuitive, and aesthetically pleasing for users of all kinds.

Experience

Controlco - UX Designer/Front End Developer

September 2016 - October 2017

- Created wireframes, lo-fi/hi-fi mock-ups, and prototypes for IoT building automation applications
- Re-designed mobile BAS applications and websites
- Designed and developed dashboards, alarm consoles, and other entities to track building innerworkings using HTML/CSS and Javascript
- Used DGLux5 in conjunction with Niagara 4 to connect back-end points to UI for fully interactive data

KM Consulting - UX/Visual Designer

August 2014 - July 2016

- Created wireframes of user flow for both mobile and desktop applications
- Worked with a team of engineers, information architects, and other designers to ideate and delegate tasks
- Conduct user research and usability testing through common methodologies like A/B testing and auestionaires
- Designed icons and visual content using Illustrator

Freelance - Graphic Designer

August 2008 - Current

- Design both digital and print collateral using Illustrator, Photoshop, and InDesign
- Come up with creative concepts for clients
- Create digital paintings and scalable graphics

Education

University of California, Santa Barbara

September 2012 - June 2014

Bachelor of Science, Biological Sciences

Areas of Expertise

| Sketch | Photoshop |
|-------------|---------------|
| InVision | Illustrator |
| Wireframing | AutoCAD |
| Prototyping | Final Cut |
| HTML/CSS | Corel Painter |
| InDesign | Petting Cats |